[Music]
hello everyone I'm Jessica Carr from
Jim's rohini sector 5. currently I'm
pursuing pgtm in international business
specializing in finance it gives me an
immense pleasure to share with you all
that I'm placed in Deloitte I must say
gym Sector 5 rohini has provided me with
a platform with the thorough of
opportunities and great learnings with
the constant support guidance and
motivation of all my faculty mentors and
especially the crmc department I've been
able to achieve this success also I've
learned a lot in my college not just
academically but also in other aspects
of career development my journey so far
in Jim's rohini Sector 5 has been
phenomenal and has helped me evolve
myself professionally and personally
I've established leadership time
management and team skills and I've been
able to advance these skills to a whole
new level I'm grateful and proud to be a
part of Jim Sony sector 5.
foreign